[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "category": "food",
        "question": "What was the first soft drink in space?",
        "answer": "Coca Cola",
        "option": [
            "Sprite",
            "Coca Cola",
            "Fanta",
            "Pepsi"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "category": "gk",
        "question": "Which monarch officially made Valentine's Day a holiday in 1537?",
        "answer": "Henry",
        "option": [
            "Wesley",
            "Henry",
            "Dean",
            "Edward"
        ] 
        
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "category": "entertainment",
        "question": "What position does Harry play on the Quidditch team?",
        "answer": "Seeker",
        "option": [
            "Finder",
            "Keeper",
            "Chaser",
            "Seeker"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "category": "gk",
        "question": "What's the smallest country in the world?",
        "answer": "Vatican City",
        "option": [
            "Hobart",
            "Bolzano",
            "Vatican City",
            "Lausanne"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "category": "music",
        "question": "The biggest selling music single of all time is?",
        "answer": "Candle in the Wind",
        "option": [
            "I'll Be Missing You",
            "Hypnotize",
            "Candle in the Wind",
            "Un-Break My Heart"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "category": "food",
        "question": "How would you say 'house wine' in 'Italian'?",
        "answer": "Vino Della Casa",
        "option": [
            "Vino Della Casa",
            "Barbera",
            "Cabernet Sauvignon",
            "Syrah"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "category": "game",
        "question": "What is another name for the card game 'Blackjack'?",
        "answer": "21",
        "option": [
            "Patience",
            "Koi-Koi",
            "21",
            "Go Fish"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "category": "gk",
        "question": "What does the Greek root word 'chrom' mean?",
        "answer": "Color",
        "option": [
            "Soul",
            "Color",
            "Sorrow",
            "Chilled"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "category": "entertainment",
        "question": "Who was able to pick up Thor's hammer in Endgame?",
        "answer": "Captain America",
        "option": [
            "Captain America",
            "Thor",
            "Iron Man",
            "Hulk"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "category": "gk",
        "question": "What is the smallest perfect number?",
        "answer": "6",
        "option": [
            "12",
            "6",
            "3",
            "9"
        ]
    }
]